https://www.susanstripling.com/privacy-policy

Shop
Contact Blog IcelandGreen-Wood CemeteryBroadway Shutdown 20201 Hotel Brooklyn Bridge26 Bridge501 Union620 Loft and GardenAbove Rooftop LoungeAldrich MansionAndaz Wall StreetAngel OrensanzArts BallroomBallroom at Ellis PreserveBarns at Wesleyan HillsBasilica HudsonBattery GardensBedell CellarsBelle MerBerkeley Oceanfront HotelBlue Hill at Stone BarnsBonnet IslandBowery HotelBridgehampton Tennis and Surf ClubBrooklyn Botanic GardenBryant Park GrillCairnwood EstateCapitaleCaramoorCarnegie MuseumCentral Park Boathouse/Loeb BoathouseChubb Conference CenterCipriani 42nd StreetCollege of Physicians/Mutter MuseumColony ClubCongress HallCrossed Keys InnCrystal PlazaCrystal Tea RoomDaviosDominick HotelDoubleTree by Hilton SomersetEstate at Florentine GardensFitler ClubFlowerfieldFonthill Castle/Mercer MuseumThe FoundryFox HollowFrogbridgeFront and PalmerGarrisonGiando on the WaterGibbert BarnGiorgio's Baiting HollowGotham HallGramercy Park HotelGrand Historic VenueGrandviewThe Green BuildingGurney's MontaukHall of SpringsHeldrich HotelHempstead House/Sands Point PreserveHickoriesHill at HudsonHolly Hedge EstateHotel DuPontHotel DuVillageHotel Monaco PhiladelphiaHyatt at the BellevueKimmel CenterJasna PolanaThe Lake House InnLiberty HouseLiberty WarehouseThe Library HotelLighthouse at Chelsea Piers/Pier SixtyLoews Hotel PhiladelphiaLogan HotelLongwood GardensLord Thompson ManorMadison HotelMallard Island Yacht ClubMandarin OrientalManhattan City HallManhattan PenthouseThe Mansion at Glen CoveMaritime ParcMetLife StadiumMetropolitan BuildingThe MerionThe Molly Pitcher InnMorris House HotelNassau InnNew York Palace/Burden Kahn MansionThe Ocean HouseOcean Place Resort and SpaOheka CastleOld Field ClubOld Westbury GardensOnteora Mountain HousePalace at SomersetPark ChateauPark SavoyPearl River HiltonPen RynPine Hollow Country ClubThe PierrePlaza HotelPleasantdale ChateauPlease Touch MuseumPowel HousePrince George BallroomPrinceton UniversityProspect Park BoathouseRed Lion InnRitz Carlton PhiladelphiaRiverside FarmRiviera Waterfront MansionRock Island Lake ClubThe RockleighRoosevelt HotelRose Bank WineryThe RoundhouseSaltwater FarmSenate GarageShadowbrook at ShrewsburyShelburne FarmsSkylight WestSleepy Hollow Country ClubSpring Mill Country ClubStamford Yacht ClubState RoomStone Mill/New York Botanical GardenStonover FarmStudio 450St.RegisSurf Club New RochelleSweetwater Farms/Grace WineryTarrytown House EstateTop of the RockTribeca RooftopUnion LeagueUnion TrustThe Wagner at the BatteryWave HillWest Hills Country ClubWestin PhiladelphiaWhitby CastleWoodwindsWythe HotelVenues 1-B
Venues C-F
Venues G-L
Venues M-P
Venues Q-T
Venues U-Z
General InformationWedding Day TimelineAlbumsGetting ReadyFirst LookFamily PortraitsWedding Day PortraitsEngagement SessionsFrom the Internet : Questions to Ask Your Wedding PhotographerDo I Need a Second Photographer For My Wedding?The Importance of Family PortraitsWhat I Learned From Planning My Own WeddingHow To Care For Your Wedding Day Digital FilesAsk This, Not That : The Wedding Photography EditionThe Wedding Photography ProcessAbout My Style Frequent Questions Prices and Packages New York Elopements Wedding Venues
Wedding Planning Tips
Additional Articles
Reviews Slideshows NYC Headshot PhotographyArticles and PressAwards and FeaturesNew York Location TipsNYC HotelsPhiladelphia Location TipsPhotography Services + Pricing Wedding Photography
Portrait and Headshot Photography
Awards and Press
Vendor Recommendations Photo Locations
Real Estate/Interiors EducationWedding Photography Equipment ListCareersFloral, Cemetery, and Cityscape Print ShopArt Shop : Paintings
Home »
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyEffective date: October 07, 2018Susan Stripling Photography, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.susanstripling.com website (the "Service").This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataSusan Stripling Photography, LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Susan Stripling Photography, LLC will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal RequirementsSusan Stripling Photography, LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Susan Stripling Photography, LLCTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enLinks To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children's PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: susan@susanstripling.com
Privacy Policy.
